Ezekiel Fajuyagbe

- **♥** Ibadan, Nigeria
- **≤** fajuyabeezekiel90@gmail.com
- **** 09079709430
- **in** Fajuyagbe Ezekiel
- sunshine-web-coder

PROFILE

Dedicated Frontend developer with 3 years' experience in creating responsive and userfriendly web applications with clean code. Proficient in JavaScript, React Js, HTML, CSS, and modern frontend libraries and frameworks. I have helped clients build small and medium level web applications from the first line of code to the end.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

06/2020 - 09/2020

Frontend Developer (Intern), HNG



It is a learn-in job role, I work alongside Team members to complete each project.

- Mastered front-end Object-oriented programming to develop a client-server system
- Working with different UI/UX designers to complete different websites (as the tasks instructed)
- Working with different frontend developers as a team.

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Figma, Git, Bootstrap

08/2021 - 10/2022

Frontend Developer (Contract), Vince Chain

Remote

I worked on various websites as a frontend developer

- Built & assists in the deployment of the websites
- Coding scalable websites from scratch
- Maintaining code issues and debugging, while also solving client's issues
- Works on website templates and solve code issues and debugging
- Actively collaborating with design team to convert design to
- Suggesting findings & research to key decision-makers

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, Figma, Git, Bootstrap, Tailwindcss

SKILLS

Tools & Methods Technical

GitHub, Slack, Google Meet, Zoom JavaScript, Git, Debugging Code, UI & UX, ES6, JSON, DOM

Professional

Leadership Ability, Time Optimization, Effective Communication, Teamwork, Flexibility, Project management, Enthusiasm for Personal Growth, Designing for Positive User Experiences

Hard Skill

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, Tailwindcss, Git, Rest API, SCSS, Node Js

EDUCATION

2006 - 2009 **General Certificate of Education(GCE),** Baptist Senior High

School

08/2019 - 11/2019 **HTML, CSS & Javascript for web developers,** Starting

Remotely I acquired a comprehensive understanding of Frontend

Development through the completion of various tasks using

HTML, CSS, JavaScript as the development tools